Now if we save half the fuel then the world will remain There is a
smile on every face Or if we
keep the moon in the world then there will be a
smile on every face There will be happiness only
when we take care of the traffic rules If we keep the life then the world will remain
Nirhu There will be a smile on every face Come and see, see the style But the
eyes will always be on the front You may also want to get, see the view
Shyam has not moved from the road Beautiful life,
simple, long life, fun for a long life Police camp if we keep the life then the world will remain There is a
smile on every face
Pujara has no compulsion Helmet is not your
unnecessary seat belt Protect the family
golden distance Watch the traffic signal
Stop at the red light Get ready on the number and
then proceed on green Never
stop only on or ahead of the promising Do
n't drive your car in the conference To avoid traffic jams,
don't talk on the mobile and
stay away from intoxicants Overtake, keep the air Parsi and
speed camphor
We have to drive on the road after taking license at the right age If we know then the world will remain
Nirhu There will be a smile on every face There will be
happiness only when we take
care of the traffic rules If we know then the world will remain Nirkh There will be a
smile on every face Beautiful days,
good massage for a long life  If Sunidhi Chauhan
keeps it, there will be a smile on every face wherever she is.